yourtv.link 2018-01-12

# Your Tv Link - Privacy Policy

The following Privacy Policy discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for [YourTV.link](http://yourtv.link/).

[YourTV.link](http://yourtv.link/) uses cookies from third-party vendors for the purpose of advertising. They are used in the following way:

  * Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to your website.
  * Google's use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting [Ads Settings](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/).

Additionally, users can set their browsers to accept or reject all, or certain, cookies. To learn more about how to manage cookies, visit [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/)

Like many other websites, [YourTV.link](http://yourtv.link/) collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP address, your ISP, your browser's User-Agent string, the time you visited our site and which pages you visited. All of this information is not linked to anything that is personally identifiable.

[YourTV.link](http://yourtv.link/) contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of these or any other websites. Concerned users should review each website's privacy policy page to learn how that site collects and uses data.

We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time and without prior notice, by posting the revised version on [YourTV.link/privacy](http://yourtv.link/privacy). Users are encouraged to review the Privacy Policy from time to time.

Please contact us with any questions about this website Privacy Policy.
